TO UNDERSTAND A MAN’S PSYCHOLOGY
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND HOW
HE WAS CONDITIONED FROM THE
MOMENT HE TOOK HIS FIRST
BREATH ON THIS PLANET MEN
ARE RARELY VALUED FOR SIMPLY
EXISTING A WOMAN IS OFTEN
VALUED FOR WHO SHE IS
BUT A MAN IS ALMOST
EXCLUSIVELY VALUED FOR WHAT HE
CAN PROVIDE PROTECT AND BUILD
FROM BOYHOOD A MAN LEARNS
THAT HIS SAFETY IN THE
TRIBE IS TIED DIRECTLY TO
ONE THING HIS COMPETENCE HIS
EMOTIONAL SELF-WORTH ISN'T STORED IN
A WARM FUZZY BOX OF
AFFECTION IT IS FORGED INTO
AN ARMOR PLATE WHEN THE
WORLD RESPECTS HIS COMPETENCE HE
FEELS SAFE BUT THE MOMENT
HIS COMPETENCE IS QUESTIONED HIS
BRAIN INTERPRETS IT AS AN
EXISTENTIAL THREAT IT MEANS HE
HAS FAILED HIS PRIMARY REASON
FOR BEING AND THAT BRINGS
US TO THE DEADLY TRAP
THAT CATCHES WOMEN COMPLETELY OFF
GUARD